# ∘ADOLPHUS MIRACLE O. ⊶

**FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER** 

Email: miraboy13@gmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/adolphus-miracle

Phone: +234 9093386514, +234 8026889782 | GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/m4-programmer">https://github.com/m4-programmer</a>

## ACTIVITIES AND INTEREST

Travel | Music | Developing |
Problem Solving | Mathematics

### **OBJECTIVES**

I am a Full stack web developer, a Multi-tasker, Self-Motivated and Result driven developer. I have **5+ years** experience in web development as a front and backend developer and as a database analyst. I love impacting knowledge by teaching and solving real life problems using my skillset.

#### COMPUTING SKILLS

- HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT
- BOOTSTRAP | JQUERY
- REACT | REACTNATIVE
- PHP| LARAVEL| MYSQL| SQL
- PYTHON | DJANGO | FLASK
- API | GIT | GITHUB
- DOCKER

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Backend Engineer at M4WebMetrix – (August 2021 – Present)
PHP | LARAVEL | MYSQL | PYTHON | DJANGO | GIT | GITHUB

Full Stack Engineer at MEDIA MALL – (Oct 2020 – Feb 2021) PHP | LARAVEL | MYSQL | PYTHON | DJANGO | GIT | GITHUB

Freelance Web Developer – (Jan 2017 – August 2020) PHP | MYSQL | JAVASCRIPT | JQUERY | BOOSTRAP | CSS | HTML

#### **EDUCATION**

B.SC in Computer Statistics -University of Nigeria Nsukka (UNN)

2017 - present

WAEC - Comprehensive Secondary School Eleme – Port Harcourt

2011 - 2017

#### **PROJECTS**

**VMS**: A web-based visitor management system with image taking functionality.

 $\begin{array}{c} \textbf{PHP} \mid \textbf{MYSQL} \mid \textbf{JAVASCRIPT} \mid \textbf{JQUERY} \mid \textbf{BOOSTRAP} \mid \textbf{CSS} \mid \textbf{HTML} \\ \underline{\textbf{view project}} \end{array}$ 

A Restful API with Flask: A basic api with register, login and template route.

PYTHON | FLASK | MONGODB ATLAS | JWT view project on GitHub

visit website

**Student Junk Shop**: A web-based e – commerce system for students.

 $\begin{aligned} & \textbf{PHP} \mid \textbf{MYSQL} \mid \textbf{JAVASCRIPT} \mid \textbf{JQUERY} \mid \textbf{BOOSTRAP} \mid \textbf{CSS} \mid \textbf{HTML} \\ & \underline{\textbf{view project}} \end{aligned}$